

123 Bedford Avenue, New York, NY, 12345

Jessica Lang@ example.com
(123) 456-7890

An IT Manager with 10+ years of experience specializing in developing, implementing, and maintaining IT infrastructure. A proven track record of leading diverse teams to execute large-scale integration projects and drive process improvements to enhance system reliability.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### IT MANAGER

Excelsior Technology, New York, NY I November 2015 - Present

- Oversee infrastructure and system architecture supporting North America operations across four offices with 130+ personnel and 100+workstations
- Lead a team of 30 IT Specialists, System Administrators, and Software Engineers, evaluate performance, and provide coaching and mentorship to team members
- Serve as a member of the Cyber Security Committee, interface with C-level executives, and deliver monthly
  presentations on project status and performance metrics

#### **IT MANAGER**

Brookyn Telecom, New York, NY May 2011 - November 2015

- Coordinated with the DevOps team and Project Management Organization (PMO) to migrate critical services from on-premises to cloud infrastructure, which ensured 99,99% server uptime and generated a \$150K reduction in annual costs
- Led the development and implementation of business continuity plans and disaster recovery protocols for the organization, which included conducting IT audits

# **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE (B.S.)
INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Columbia University, New York, NSeptember 2007 - May 2011

# **KEY SKILLS**

- IT Management
- ♦ Cross-Functional Leadership
- Disaster Recovery
- Project Management
- ♦ Technical Leadership

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Certified Information Technology Manager (CITM),2015
- Project Management Professional (PMP), 2013
- CompTIA Network+, 2011